http://www.chifley.com/terms-of-use

Terms of Use
Chifley Services Pty Ltd atf Chifley Trading Trust (ACN 630 582 857) (Chifley) abides by the Australian Privacy Principles (APP) set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (the “Act”). Chifley’s Privacy Policy is available on application.Why we collect your personal information?Chifley is responsible for the efficient operation of its financial services business including its activities as the corporate authorised representative of two (2) Australian Financial Services Licence Holders (AFSL No.245377 and AFSL No. 238874). In the ordinary course of those operations, Chifley collects personal information, including sensitive information, about individuals both directly from those individuals and from others, including from agents or employers. Chifley does not collect personal information not required for these purposes.What kind of information do we collect?Personal information collected includes name, address, date of birth, employment details (date commenced, salary) and ongoing records of contributions made by individuals in superannuation and other financial products.Equivalent information is collected to enable preparation of financial plans. We may ask you for the following information:Drivers licence, passport and medicare card;Employment details and employment history;Details of your financial needs and objectives;Details of your current financial circumstances, including your assets and liabilities (both actual and potential), income, expenditure, insurance cover and superannuation;Details of your investment preferences and aversion or tolerance to risk;Your family circumstances;Estate planning detailsSocial security benefits;Sensitive health information (for some types of insurance);Bank and investments account details;Chess Holder ID Numbers (HIN); andTax File Number.Failure to provide the personal and sensitive information referred to above may expose you to higher risks in respect of the recommendations made to you and may affect the adequacy or appropriateness of financial service or advice we give to you.We will not collect any personal information about you except when you have knowingly provided that information to us or authorised a third party to provide that information to us. Generally collection of your personal information will be effected in face to face interviews (when we ask you to bring certain information), over the telephone or by completion of a fact find or client profile form. From time to time additional and/or updated personal information may be collected through one or more of those methods.How we collectMost information is collected when you become a client of one of the financial services that we make available. But there may be other ways we collect personal information such as through contact with you and from your agent, employer, accountant or solicitor. We will collect personal information from you only by lawful and fair means and not in an unreasonably intrusive way.How do we use your personal information and who might we disclose it to?We will only use personal information about you if it is necessary for us to adequately provide to you the services you have requested including:making insurance recommendations;implementing recommendations made to you and accepted by you;reviewing your insurance;supporting the services offered to you by another insurance financial services provider; andforwarding your personal details to a third party for the administration of a services you have requested.This information is not disclosed to or accessed by any other party except as follows:where the person has consented to the disclosure;where Chifley uses a service provider (such as an administrator) to carry out its obligations, personal information is disclosed to or accessed by that service provider only where there is a contractual requirement that the service provider abide by the APPs and the Act in the same manner as Chifley and applies Chifley’s Privacy Policy;to other organisations providing services to Chifley for the purpose of providing access to a financial product e.g. home loans, insurance or superannuation;where required or authorised by law (eg the Tax Office requires reporting of various information in relation to the surcharge and at the time a benefit is paid); and/ormedical information provided in relation to an application for cover for insured benefits or in relation to a claim for an invalidity benefit.How do we store personal information?Your personal information is stored securely and is generally held in your client file. Information may also be held in a computer database. We will use our best endeavours to ensure that the personal information collected and held by us is protected from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.If you cease to be a client, any personal information which we retain about you will be maintained for a period of 7 years in order to comply with legislative and professional requirements.You have the right to check your personal informationYou may request access to your personal information by contacting your adviser or our Privacy Officer. We will provide you with access to that information either by providing you with copies of the information requested, allowing you to inspect the information requested or providing you with an accurate summary of the information held. We will, prior to providing access in accordance with this policy, require you to provide evidence of your identity.The Act does have some exceptions to your right to access. If we refuse you access to your personal information, we will provide you with an explanation for that refusal.We will endeavour to ensure that, at all times, the personal information about you which we hold is up to date and accurate. If you become aware, or believe, that any personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out-dated, you may contact your adviser or our Privacy Officer and provide evidence of the inaccuracy or incompleteness or obsolescence and we will, if we agree that the information requires correcting, take all reasonable steps to correct the information.If we do not agree that your personal information requires correcting, we must, if you request, take reasonable steps to ensure that whenever your personal information is accessed or handled in the future, it is apparent that you are not satisfied as to the accuracy or completeness of that information.We will endeavour to respond to any request for access within 14-30 days depending on the complexity of the information and/or the request. If your request is urgent please indicate this clearly.You may apply to the following officer in relation to any privacy issue, including access, changes to incorrect personal information, copies of the Privacy Policy and general inquiries:Privacy OfficerChifley Services Pty LtdLevel 26, Tower One, International Towers,100 Barangaroo Avenue,Barangaroo NSW 2000T: (02) 9376 7888Complaints resolutionIf you have a formal complaint about the way that Chifley handles your personal information and you are not satisfied with the response from the Privacy Officer, you may contact:Complaints Resolution OfficerChifley Services Pty LtdLevel 26, Tower One, International Towers,100 Barangaroo Avenue,Barangaroo NSW 2000If you are not satisfied with the response provided by the Complaints Resolution Officer, you may take your complaint to:Office of the Australian Information CommissionerGPO Box 5218SYDNEY NSW 2001Telephone: 1300 363 992
Want to know more?
©2019 Copyright Chifley Services Pty Ltd | Site by Intelligent Developments
Privacy Statement | Terms of Use | Financial Services Guide
